https://www.ais-york.com/ais-online-privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.ais-york.com and Advanced Industrial Services, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Advanced Industrial Services, Inc. include www.ais-york.com, AIS Inc., AIS Graphic Services, Inc. and www.ais-york.com. The AIS Inc. website is a News & Information site. By using the AIS Inc. website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
TRUSTe Privacy Program
AIS Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at Jim@aisyork.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint. TRUSTe may serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.
Collection of your Personal Information
We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by AIS Inc.. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the AIS Inc.website.
AIS Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from AIS Inc. so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. AIS Inc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the AIS Inc. website.
Security of your Personal Information
AIS Inc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Children Under Thirteen
AIS Inc. does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from AIS Inc. by contacting us here:
Web page: www.ais-york.com
Email: info@ais-york.com
Phone: 717-764-9811
Changes to this Statement
AIS Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. AIS Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how AIS Inc. is protecting your information.
Contact Information
AIS Inc. welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that AIS Inc. has not adhered to this Statement, please contact AIS Inc. at:
Advanced Industrial Services, Inc.
Ready to get started?
Request a Quote
